Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:I: Individuals.
    - Seeley, David S., undated (Item 438)
    - Seeley, Mae, undated (Item 890)
    - Selden, David, undated (Item 257)
    - Selden, David addressing luncheon session, May 1973 (Item 2541)
    - Seligmann, Ernie, undated (Item 1017)
    - Seminara, Joseph, Dist. 20 Election Candidate, Apr 1973 (Item 1139)
    - Senior, Clarence and Mr. Daniels, undated (Item 157)
    - Senior, Clarence, Portrait, undated (Item 157)
    - Settle, John congratulates winners of Martin Luther King Memorial Awards, Jun 1975 (Item 3811)
    - Seymour, Whitney North Jr. (Senator), undated (Item 95)
    - Shaffer, Doris, President, Nassau Community College, undated (Item 3366)
    - Shalala, Donna, undated (Item 5677)
    - Shalala, Donna, Dr., Mar 1975 (Item 3648)
    - Shanas, undated (Item 5676)
    - Shane, Jaqui, presents Al Shanker with check for AFT Defense Fund, Aug 1975 (Item 3854)
    - Shank, Alan, Pres. Of SUC / Geneseo, May 1981 (Item 5429)
    - Shanker, Al agrees to invest NY Teachers' Retirement System Funds for Big Mac Bonds, Oct 1975 (Item 4110)
    - Shanker, Al and Crisis Commission hold Press Conference, Jan 1976 (Item 3980)
    - Shanker, Al and George Meany, AFL-CIO VP, Nov 1973 (Item 2768)
    - Shanker, Al and school secretaries at cocktail party, Oct 1972 (Item 2055)
    - Shanker, Al answering questions at Long Island Forum, Jan 28, 1973 (Item 2181)
    - Shanker, Al at AFT Convention, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al at Award Presentation with Robert F. Wagner, undated (Item 2181)
    - Shanker, Al at Board of Education Hearing, undated (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al at City Hall, 1968 (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al at Dutchess County County Teachers Council, Oct 1974 (Item 3450)
    - Shanker, Al at Dutchess County Teachers Council, Nov 1974 (Item 3318)
    - Shanker, Al at Forest Hills HS, Queens, Nov 1976 (Item 4043)
    - Shanker, Al at HEW Conference, Sep 1974 (Item 3294)
    - Shanker, Al at Lafayette HS, Brooklyn, Feb 1976 (Item 4043)
    - Shanker, Al at NYS School Board Convention, Oct 1973 (Item 2769)
    - Shanker, Al at Paraprofessionals meeting, 1976 (Item 4573)
    - Shanker, Al at Press Conference, Dec 12, 1972 (Item 2090)
    - Shanker, Al at press conference, undated (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al at press conference with Leon Keyserling, undated (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al at School Secretaries cocktail party, Oct 1971 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al at Stuyvesant [High School], May 1976 (Item 4424)
    - Shanker, Al at Stuyvesant HS, undated (Item 4043)
    - Shanker, Al being interviewed by Bill Moyers, Apr 1974 (Item 2984)
    - Shanker, Al being interviewed by Geraldo Rivera, Apr 1973 (Item 2181)
    - Shanker, Al during Press Conference at American Jewish Congress, undated (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al honored at Jewish Labor Committee Dinner, Dec 1975 (Item 3958)
    - Shanker, Al in Eastern LI District 12, Nov 1972 (Item 2090)
    - Shanker, Al meeting with Japanese union leaders, Dec 1973 (Item 2810)
    - Shanker, Al meets with Crisis Commission in New York City Schools, Oct 1975 (Item 4106)
    - Shanker, Al meets with German unionists representing metal workers, mine workers, chemical workers, and public service communications workers, Nov 1974 (Item 3475)
    - Shanker, Al on "Voice of the Teacher," WEVD Radio, Feb 1976 (Item 3988)
    - Shanker, Al on TV (Brinkley and News Forum, Ch. 4, Sunday), Mar 31, 1985 (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al presenting award to Shalom Levin, Apr 1974 (Item 3025)
    - Shanker, Al presenting check for West African Famine relief fund, undated (Item 3183)
    - Shanker, Al Press Conference in New Orleans, State Feds meeting, Dec 1974 (Item 3470)
    - Shanker, Al Press Conference on Budget Cuts at Gramercy Park Hotel, Jun 1975 (Item 3729)
    - Shanker, Al Press Conference, Gramercy Park, Oct 9, 1975 (Item 3911)
    - Shanker, Al receives the distinguished Educator Award of 1974, Jun 1974 (Item 3132)
    - Shanker, Al Reception in New York, undated (Item 1360)
    - Shanker, Al speaking, undated (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at Central Commercial HS, Apr 22, 1971 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at District 16 Meeting, Apr 20, 1971 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at IS 131 Bronx, Jan 11, 1971 (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at JHS 51 Richmond, Mar 17, 1971 (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at Saratoga, Apr 1974 (Item 3015)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at School Superintendents' Convention, Jul 17, 1972 (Item 1130)
    - Shanker, Al speaking at Susquehanna Valley, Oct 27, 1972 (Item 2090)
    - Shanker, Al speaking on Soviet Jewry, May 26, 1971 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al speaking to members of [NYSUT Local?] Elwood Federation of Teachers, Jan 7, 1972 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al speaks at John Adams HS, Dec 1975 (Item 4043)
    - Shanker, Al testifies before State Legislature Pension Group, undated (Item 1128)
    - Shanker, Al urges state teachers to fight for decent pacts, Jun 1973 (Item 2603)
    - Shanker, Al urging State Teachers to Fight for Decent Contracts, Jun 1973 (Item 1130)
    - Shanker, Al Welcome Home Party (also Selden), Jun 9, 1970 (Item 1130)
    - Shanker, Al with AFT President Dave Seldon and Tom Hobart (merger pix), undated (Item 2698)
    - Shanker, Al with Alexander Solhenitzyn, Jul 1975 (Item 3787)
    - Shanker, Al with Allen Johnson, May 1974 (Item 3070)
    - Shanker, Al with Barry Feinstein, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Bayard Rustin, undated (Item 1130)
    - Shanker, Al with Dan Sanders, undated (Item 1130)
    - Shanker, Al with Daniel P. Moynihan, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Ernest Boyer, Commissioner of Education, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Felix Rodriguez (President of Puerto Rico Federation of Teachers), Dec 1973 (Item 2806)
    - Shanker, Al with Felix Rohatyn, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Gordon Ambach, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Governor Rockefeller and others, undated (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al with Hugh Carey at AFL-CIO Convention, Sep 1974 (Item 3320)
    - Shanker, Al with Israel Kugler, undated (Item 2181)
    - Shanker, Al with James Harris and Barbara Walters on the 'Today' Show, Mar 1975 (Item 3585)
    - Shanker, Al with Jeanette Pietrani and Loretta Donlon, Jun 13, 1976 (Item 4458)
    - Shanker, Al with Jim Harris on 'Today' Show with Barbara Walters, Mar 1975 (Item 3606)
    - Shanker, Al with John Matthews and Tom Joyce at Labor News Conference, Dec 1974 (Item 3462)
    - Shanker, Al with Jules Kolodny and Smallheiser Award Winners Mel Aaronson, Ruth Melton, Eugene Blum, Goldie Colodny, Sol Levine, Sol Jaffe, Charles Cogen, George Altomare, Charles Miller and Ray Frankle, undated (Item 109)
    - Shanker, Al with Lillian Roberts, undated (Item 2181)
    - Shanker, Al with Mervyn Dymally at JLC Convention, Nov 1973 (Item 2763)
    - Shanker, Al with Nicholas Harding, May 1974 (Item 3059)
    - Shanker, Al with Robert Christen and Joseph Macchiarola, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al with Samuel Paul Holmes, Jan 1974 (Item 2812)
    - Shanker, Al with Sandra Feldman and Al Lowenthal, Jan 1974 (Item 2816)
    - Shanker, Al with Senator Jacob Javits, 1974 (Item 2949)
    - Shanker, Al with Senator Jacob Javits at UFT Spring Conference, 1979 (Item 2949)
    - Shanker, Al with Senator Walter F. Mondale and 11 re-elected vice presidents, undated (Item 4527)
    - Shanker, Al with Senator Walter F. Mondale at AFT Convention, undated (Item 4527)
    - Shanker, Al with Senator Wayne Morse, undated (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al with Student NYSTA, Mar 1974 (Item 2907)
    - Shanker, Al with Tom Cunningham, Nov 30, 1971 (Item 1572)
    - Shanker, Al with Tom Hobart at Binghamton, Feb 1976 (Item 4001)
    - Shanker, Al with Zeev Haring and Irving Heller, 1970 (Item 161)
    - Shanker, Al, Macchiarola, undated (Item 5033)
    - Shanker, Al, "Where We Stand" column in Chinese, undated (Item 1100)
    - Shanker, Al, "Where We Stand" column in English, undated (Item 1100)
    - Shanker, Al, at AFL-CIO Convention 1984 [x], undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, at AFT Convention, 1978 (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, BOCES, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, Brooklyn Tech HS, Dec 1976 (Item 4043)
    - Shanker, Al, Carl Megel, and VP Humphrey, undated (Item 200)
    - Shanker, Al, Cartoon, Is it still OK to hate Shanker?, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, Department for Professional Employees, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, Don Burns, and Dale McFeatters at Press Conference, Feb 1976 (Item 4313)
    - Shanker, Al, Labor Leaders, 1975 (Item 3605)
    - Shanker, Al, letter from George Meany re 10th Anniversary, undated (Item 1100)
    - Shanker, Al, Letter from Harry Van Arsdale re 10th Anniversary, undated (Item 1100)
    - Shanker, Al, NYSUT Board, Mar 1978 (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, PEC [Public Employees Conference?], undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, Residency, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, Sol Levine, Kiyotaka Yoneda, Koh-Ichiroh Konaya, and Chiyokichi Yoshimoto, Nov 1973 (Item 2792)
    - Shanker, Al, SUNY, undated (Item 35)
    - Shanker, Al, UUP Delegate Assembly, Mar 1975 (Item 3597)
    - Shanker, Michael, 1982 (Item 5573)
    - Shannon, Joseph, sworn in as Teacher-member of NYC Teachers' Retirement Board, May 1981 (Item 3712)
    - Shapiro, Elliott, undated (Item 1796)
    - Shapiro, Elliott, Demonstration, undated (Item 155)
    - Shapiro, Jay, undated (Item 641)
    - Shapiro, Leo, May 1971 (Item 1541)
    - Shapiro, Lillian, undated (Item 399)
    - Shapiro, Morris, undated (Item 16)
    - Shapiro, Morris addresses meeting of Electronics Subcommittee, Jul 1975 (Item 3825)
    - Shapiro, Morris speaking with Donald Manes, Queens Borough Pres. And (right) Dr. Sherry Friedman, former Queens Vocational HS principal, Dec 1971 (Item 1636)
    - Shapiro, Morris, Trade Teachers Demonstration, undated (Item 406)
    - Shapiro, Rose, undated (Item 279)
    - Shapiro, Rose Swearing In, Feb 10, 1970 (Item 1328)
    - Shapp, Charles M., undated (Item 1615)
    - Sharoff, Brian, undated (Item 1970)
    - Sharp, Rick, undated (Item 4709)
    - Shaw, Daisy, Director of NYC BOE and Vocational Guidance was named counselor of the year, May 1976 (Item 4377)
    - Shaw, Maye A., Dist. 11 CSB, Apr 1973 (Item 2474)
    - Shea, Dennis, Mar 1974 (Item 2901)
    - Shea, Dennis, undated (Item 2913)
    - Shebar, Charles, undated (Item 176)
    - Sheedy, James, profile shot, Mar 1982 (Item 5543)
    - Sheiner, Belle (Mt. Vernon), May 1976 (Item 4279)
    - Sheiner, Belle, PTA Convention / NYSUT Booth, 1980 (Item 4279)
    - Sherman, David B., AFT QuEST Conference, May 1, 1981 (Item 4162)
    - Sherman, Rod, Mar 1, 1975 (Item 3701)
    - Sheskin, Andy, undated (Item 5621)
    - Shields, Dorothy, AFL-CIO Department of Education Director on Labor News Conference, May 1981 (Item 2397)
    - Shkhanovich, Yury, Dec 1973 (Item 2841)
    - Shore, Barbara, undated (Item 2389)
    - Shortino, Mario, Feb 1974 (Item 2940)
    - Shulman, Michael, undated (Item 5693)
    - Shulman, Ruth, undated (Item 5067)
    - Shultz, George P., undated (Item 874)
    - Sibelman, Larry, Aug 1971 (Item 1594)
    - Sichenze, Andrew, undated (Item 2381)
    - Sickert, Walter, City of Berlin, Nov 1973 (Item 2759)
    - Siegel, Herb, undated (Item 970)
    - Siemiller, P.L., undated (Item 647)
    - Silberman, Charles, undated (Item 618)
    - Siller, Sid, May 1973 (Item 2560)
    - Silver, Bernard, undated (Item 2355)
    - Silver, Bernard addresses school secretaries in Queens, Dec 14, 1972 (Item 2132)
    - Silver, Bernard, UFT Director of the Teachers Store, Oct 1973 (Item 2725)
    - Silver, Betty, PS 30 Queens Chapter Chairman, undated (Item 5632)
    - Silverglad, Hyman, May 1974 (Item 3043)
    - Silvergleid, Michael, Apr 1973 (Item 2411)
    - Silverman, Dorothy at NYSUT Board Meeting, undated (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy at NYSUT RA 79, 1979 (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy endorsed by NYSUT Retirement Board for re-election, Jan 1981 (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy endorsed by RA delegates, Apr 1981 (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy with Alan Karasik, undated (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy with Nick Maletta and Hiram Korpeck, undated (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Dorothy, AFT Convention, 1978 (Item 4820)
    - Silverman, Dorothy, AFT Convention, undated (Item 4820)
    - Silverman, Dorothy, Alan Karasik, undated (Item 4820)
    - Silverman, Dorothy, Retirement Board, NYSUT, undated (Item 4876)
    - Silverman, Leonard, undated (Item 956)
    - Silverstein, Milton, undated (Item 3879)
    - Silverstein, Sibyl, Dist. 30 Election Candidate, Apr 1973 (Item 622)
    - Simon, Manuel, undated (Item 4383)
    - Simon, Rose, undated (Item 3918)
    - Simon, Stanley, May 1973 (Item 2552)
    - Simon, Stanley, Bronx Borough President, at Evander Childs HS announcing funds for athletic renovation, Feb 1982 (Item 2552)
    - Simon, Stanley, District 8 Bronx, undated (Item 2552)
    - Simonson. Rebecca, Teacher Union Award, undated (Item 1012)
    - Sinnigan, Al speaking, Apr 1974 (Item 3006)
    - Sirecoff, Dorothy, Stuyvesant HS, undated (Item 5615)
    - Sissman, Jack, Mar 1973 (Item 2300)
    - Skuse, Ray, Custiodial Accounts Bill with Stavisky, Feb 1981 (Item 4544)
    - Skuse, Ray, Elmsford, Briefs teachers on current legislation, Mar 1973 (Item 2328)
    - Slaiman, Don at [AFT] State Federation Conference, Dec 1974 (Item 3470)
    - Slattery, Jerry, undated (Item 973)
    - Slattery, Nina M., Jul 1973 (Item 2463)
    - Sloan, Myron, undated (Item 1162)
    - Sloan, Suzanne, undated (Item 1915)
    - Slocum, John with Samuel Wakshull, undated (Item 4221)
    - Slowik, Judy with Nicholas Kosanovich, undated (Item 5035)
    - Small, George, LIU, RA 1984 (Item 5591)
    - Smallheiser, Albert, undated (Item 302)
    - Smith, Anthony, Park West HS asbestos problem, Jun 1979 (Item 5199)
    - Smith, Carolyn with Rhea Boland, undated (Item 5105)
    - Smith, Edward J. with Joseph D'Andrea and Tom Hobart, Oct 1974 (Item 3443)
    - Smith, Henry P. 3d, undated (Item 2110)
    - Smith, James, May 1973 (Item 2550)
    - Smith, Jean Kennedy, undated (Item 5057)
    - Sneed, Edward (Jimmy), Jun 1974 (Item 3140)
    - Sneider, John, Feb 1974 (Item 2886)
    - Sobel, Max, undated (Item 872)
    - Solarz, Stephen J., Dist. 21 Brooklyn, Apr 1981 (Item 1437)
    - Sole, John, Apr 1975 (Item 3686)
    - Sole, Rohner and Finger, Vestal, NY, Apr 1976 (Item 4395)
    - Solomon, Gerald B. H., undated (Item 3228)
    - Solomon, Seymour, undated (Item 661)
    - Solomon, Steve, undated (Item 4900)
    - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander (drawing), Mar 1974 (Item 2938)
    - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander with George Meany, Jul 1975 (Item 2938)
    - Sonko, Momodou Lamin, Financial Aid sought for young African to go to college, undated (Item 2656)
    - Sorkin, Neil, undated (Item 3876)
    - Spano, Marianna E., undated (Item 4909)
    - Spatz, Naomi speaking to South American Trade Unionists who visited UFT Headquarters, Oct 1974 (Item 3416)
    - Spencer, Dave, undated (Item 4563)
    - Spencer, Dave with Dave Timothy, May 1, 1975 (Item 3833)
    - Spencer, Dave with Jim Tromblee, Jun 1, 1975 (Item 2626)
    - Speranza, Vincent, undated (Item 595)
    - Speros, James, UFT Scholarship Winner, Jan 1976 (Item 4069)
    - Spigner, Archie, Aug 1981 (Item 5457)
    - Spillane, Robert R., undated (Item 5135)
    - Spivack, Jay, undated (Item 364)
    - Spreter, Bill, [NYSUT Local?] Hannibal TA, undated (Item 4965)
    - Spreter, Sue, Fulton TA, undated (Item 4967)
    - Sprung, Gary, undated (Item 3682)
    - Squadron, Howard, undated (Item 662)
    - Squillace, Frank, undated (Item 768)
    - Stafford, Ronald B., undated (Item 3202)
    - Stafford, Senator listens and talks as teachers raise questions on upcoming bills, Apr 1976 (Item 4331)
    - Stanton, Helen R., undated (Item 2496)
    - Stavisky, Leonard (Assembly Education Committee), Oct 1980 (Item 4184)
    - Stavisky, Leonard attending the Doctorate Association of NY educators dinner, May 1976 (Item 4428)
    - Stavisky, Leonard interviews for teleprompter Community Television by Dist. 6 Rep Bob Miller, Feb 1976 (Item 4184)
    - Stavisky, Leonard meets Rochester delegation and pledges support for legislation, Jun 6, 1976 (Item 4447)
    - Stavisky, Leonard P. (Assemblyman), undated (Item 1426)
    - Stavisky, Leonard with Dan Sanders, 1979 (Item 4184)
    - Stavisky, Leonard with Sanders, Mar 1980 (Item 4184)
    - Stein, Andrew J., Jun 1981 (Item 1702)
    - Stein, Andrew J., cocktail party for UFT leaders, Oct 1981 (Item 1702)
    - Stein, Andrew J., UFT Political Action, 1979 (Item 1702)
    - Stein, David, Yonkers FT, undated (Item 5080)
    - Steinbock, Max, undated (Item 2456)
    - Steinfeldt, William, undated (Item 3210)
    - Steingut, Robert, May 1973 (Item 2558)
    - Steingut, Stanley, undated (Item 134)
    - Steingut, Stanley with Albert Blumenthal and Perry Dureyea, Jan 1975 (Item 1558)
    - Steingut, Stanley, Belle Zeller, undated (Item 134)
    - Steingut, Stanley, dinner honoring Steingut, May 1979 (Item 4823)
    - Steingut, Stanley, Pat Koenig, undated (Item 134)
    - Stella, Anthony J., undated (Item 1916)
    - Stember, Sheila, undated (Item 1014)
    - Stepano, Marco, undated (Item 1083)
    - Stephens, Rayburn and Sid Harris, Nov 1975 (Item 4015)
    - Stern, Michael, Dist. 29 Candidate, Apr 1973 (Item 2420)
    - Sterzing, H. Keith with Robert G. Porter, Jun 1975 (Item 3798)
    - Stevens, Brian, undated (Item 3446)
    - Stevens, Dorothy, undated (Item 5025)
    - Stevens, Harold A., Justice, undated (Item 3430)
    - Stevens, Joann receiving award from James F. Macandrew (WNYE-TV) with Helen Monk, 1971 (Item 1279)
    - Stevens, Mary Art Exhibit, Nov 1964 (Item 772)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, undated (Item 1308)
    - Stewart, Ken, Dec 1973 (Item 2840)
    - Stillman, Charles B., undated (Item 275)
    - Stokes, Carl, undated (Item 860)
    - Stollar, Lou, undated (Item 4906)
    - Stollis, Jim with Natasha Decker, Jan 1974 (Item 2822)
    - Stolper, Harriet (PS 33 Manhattan), undated (Item 5343)
    - Stowell, Janet, [NYSUT Local?] Weedsport TA, undated (Item 4966)
    - Straley, Walter, undated (Item 837)
    - Stratton, Samuel S., undated (Item 1993)
    - Straub, Chester J., undated (Item 96)
    - Streif, Dean, undated (Item 1056)
    - Strezlin, Harvey L., undated (Item 3251)
    - Stripling, Peg, undated (Item 2771)
    - Strohmenger, Thomas, Apr 1973 (Item 2424)
    - Struve, Guenter, Dr., City of Berlin, Nov 1973 (Item 2757)
    - Stryker, Pat, undated (Item 4892)
    - Stuart, Waldaba, undated (Item 1005)
    - Stulberg, Louis, undated (Item 300)
    - Sturtevant, David, Feb 1974 (Item 2881)
    - Suarez, Frank, undated (Item 879)
    - Suchin, Alvin M., undated (Item 3215)
    - Summa, Dom with Bruce Bevan and Louis Kustas, Sep 1974 (Item 3292)
    - Summa, Dominick with Bruce Bevan, Jul 1973 (Item 1195)
    - Sumner, Tobias, undated (Item 1273)
    - Sussman, Maurice, undated (Item 985)
    - Sutera, Charles, undated (Item 4910)
    - Sutton, Perci, Manhattan Boro President, Jun 1973 (Item 2605)
    - Sutton, Percy Celebration, undated (Item 200)
    - Swayze, Robert, Spencerport TA President, holds meeting with Local's members, undated (Item 3966)
    - Sweeney, John J., President of SEIU honored by Workers Defense League, Clendenin Award, Oct 1981 (Item 5498)
    - Sweet, Patricia, Dec 1973 (Item 2833)
    - Sweet, Robert, Deputy Mayor, undated (Item 522)
    - Sweet, William, Mar 1973 (Item 2309)
    - Sweet, William with Harry Avrutin and David Goldman at 1976 AFL-CIO Convention (Item 4579)
    - Sweet, William with Manny Kafka, undated (Item 2923)
    - Swenson, Norman, undated (Item 1975)
    - Swiecki, Gale, undated (Item 1463)
    - Sympson, Robert L., undated (Item 2489)
    - Syquia, Susan, undated (Item 2492)
    - Szuberla, Charles, undated (Item 4939)
    - Tabb, David, Apr 1973 (Item 2442)
    - Tabert, Jim, Payroll Rep. Staten Island, Jun 1973 (Item 2650)
    - Taft, Philip, undated (Item 912)
    - Tarsio, Vincent, Aug 1985 (Item 5662)
    - Tarwater, Ron, undated (Item 4282)
    - Tauber, Robert, undated (Item 1092)
    - Tauchner, Abraham, undated (Item 252)
    - Taylor, Anna, "Queen of the Mist", undated (Item 4790)
    - Taylor, Donald, Apr 1974 (Item 2974)
    - Taylor, Lottie with Dr. Charles I. Schonhaut and Irving Dorin, Jan 1976 (Item 4208)
    - Teer, Fredrica, undated (Item 5184)
    - Tempera, Lou, Suffolk Labor Committee with Stanley Rosengarten, Joseph Dixon, John DeGregorio, undated (Item 4432)
    - Tenenberg, Harry, undated (Item 697)
    - Tepper, Glen, undated (Item 4784)
    - Terry, Charles, President, Webutuck TA, undated (Item 3840)
    - Thaler, Seymour, undated (Item 382)
    - Thant, U, UN Secretary General, undated (Item 1228)
    - Thomas, Danny receives Murray-Green-Meany Award for outstanding community service (AFL-CIO), Nov 1981 (Item 5491)
    - Thomas, Norman, undated (Item 396)
    - Thomas, Patricia with Pamela Schnierle and Bonnie Rouse, Dec 1975 (Item 4028)
    - Thomas, Piri, undated (Item 3957)
    - Thomas, Rufus conducting Coaching course, Sep 1974 (Item 3300)
    - Thompson, Helen, undated (Item 2960)
    - Thompson, Martin, undated (Item 4628)
    - Thompson, William, undated (Item 381)
    - Thornton (Litton Industries), undated (Item 503)
    - Thorp, John S. (Assemblyman), Apr 1973 (Item 2625)
    - Thurmond, Strom, undated (Item 1608)
    - Tice, Walter, undated (Item 1708)
    - Tice, Walter shares honor of being named to the National Advisory Committee with his family, Feb 9, 1975 (Item 3544)
    - Tice, Walter testimonial with Sanders, Polishook, May 1979 (Item 3544)
    - Tiger, Ivan with Simon Schwartz, Anthony DiFalco, George Fesko and Irving Witkin, undated (Item 1862)
    - Tiger, Ivan with Simon Schwartz, Irving Witkin, and Andrew Stein, undated (Item 1862)
    - Tiger, Ivan, VOTE/COPE, Jun 1979 (Item 1862)
    - Tobias, Richard, undated (Item 711)
    - Tobin, Irwin, undated (Item 971)
    - Todd, Don, undated (Item 4989)
    - Tom, Vivian, Apr 1974 (Item 2964)
    - Toomey, Bill and Ron Cocciole STA Board Members, Oct 1973 (Item 2741)
    - Topper, Sam, Montrose, Mar 1973 (Item 2329)
    - Torres, Hilda, undated (Item 4710)
    - Towne, Ken with Antonia Cortese, undated (Item 4620)
    - Tractenberg, Eli, undated (Item 699)
    - Trainor, John, undated (Item 1091)
    - Travia, Anthony J., Speaker, undated (Item 184)
    - Trela, John T., Oct 1973 (Item 2727)
    - Troisi, Victor, Jr., undated (Item 4635)
    - Tromblee, Jim with Dave Spencer, Jun 1975 (Item 3626)
    - Trombley, Mike, Jun 1975 (Item 3564)
    - Trowbridge, Edward H., undated (Item 691)
    - Troy, Matthew, undated (Item 2103)
    - Tucker, Alfred J., Mar 1973 (Item 2259)
    - Tucker, James F., undated (Item 584)
    - Tucker, Leolive, 1975 (Item 3758)
    - Tucker, Leolive, undated (Item 947)
    - Tuller, Linnie, undated (Item 2704)
    - Tunick, Adele B., undated (Item 708)
    - Turkowitz, Martin, undated (Item 695)
    - Turnbull, William W., undated (Item 1610)
    - Turner, Frances, undated (Item 431)
    - Turner, J. C., undated (Item 4527)
    - Turner, John [x], Oct 1980 (Item 5106)
    - Turner, John, C.W. Post [Long Island University Campus] President, Oct 1980 (Item 3303)
    - Turner, Richard, undated (Item 665)
    - Turner, Richard, Dr., Feb 19, 1972 (Item 1757)
    - Turner, Van L., undated (Item 693)
    - Tyler, Gus speaking to retired teachers chapter, Mar 13, 1973 (Item 2271)
    - Uba, Ron, Jun 1975 (Item 3807)
    - Uberman, Mark, undated (Item 4895)
    - Udall, Morris K., Apr 1976 (Item 4230)